Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XIII. Speeches and Writings, 1981-1991; 22.50 Linear Feet in 54 manuscript boxes.; 1 audiocassette; 3 VHS
  - Japanese NYU Alumni Association Reception (Japan), 1982-11-22 (Box 264, Folder 9)
  - Remarks Re: Library Resources, Dean's Lunch Honoring Phillip Johnson and Richard Foster (NYU), 1982-11-29 (Box 264, Folder 10)
  - Foreword, Student Financial Aid Handbook, 1982-11-29 (Box 264, Folder 11)
  - Remarks Re: the Handicapped, Blum Presidential Citation (School of Education, NYU), 1982-12-01 (Box 264, Folder 12)
  - Commerce Alumni Association Dean's Day (NYU), 1982-12-04 (Box 264, Folder 13)
  - Tribute to Reubin Seldin (NYU College of Dentistry), 1982-12-09 (Box 264, Folder 14)
  - Christmas Tree Lighting in Washington Square Park (New York, NY), 1982-12-09 (Box 264, Folder 15)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Broadway Preview (New York, NY), 1982-12-09 (Box 264, Folder 16)
  - Remarks by Dean David Oppenheim, Tisch School of the Arts Broadway Preview, 1982-12-09 (Box 264, Folder 17)
  - Memo to the Domestic Policy Study Group Center for National Policy, 1982-12-10 (Box 264, Folder 18)
  - Remarks Re: Dr. Fritz Machlup, Department of Economics Reception (NYU), 1982-12-14 (Box 264, Folder 19)
  - Reception for Leon Shimkin (NYU), 1982-12-14 (Box 264, Folder 20)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council (NYU), 1982-12-16 (Box 264, Folder 21)
  - Review of Congress and the Common Good, by Arthur Maas, 1983 (Box 264, Folder 22)
  - 35th Anniversary of the Fulbright Program in Greece (Athens, Greece), 1983-01-12 (Box 264, Folder 23)
  - Advisory Council Executive Management Training in Athens Program (Athens, Greece), 1983-01-13 (Box 264, Folder 24)
  - Remarks by Brademas and Laurence Tisch, Federal Reserve Bank of New York Dinner (Regency Hotel, NY), 1983-01-19 (Box 264, Folder 25)
  - New York Federal Executive Board (Vista Hotel, World Trade Center, NY), 1983-01-19 (Box 264, Folder 26)
  - Radio Interview Re: the Education Commission (WCBS), 1983-01-19 (Box 264, Folder 27)
  - Humphrey Award, Metropolitan Social Studies Conference (New York Hilton, NY), 1983-01-22 (Box 264, Folder 28)
  - Presidential Citation Dinner for Robert Badinter (NYU), 1983-01-22 (Box 265, Folder 1)
  - Universal Studios Luncheon Honoring John Brademas (Los Angeles, CA), 1983-01-27 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Remarks by Preston R. Tisch, Luncheon Honoring John Brademas (Los Angeles, CA), 1983-01-27 (Box 265, Folder 3)
  - Southern California Association for Philanthropy (Los Angeles, CA), 1983-01-28 (Box 265, Folder 4)
  - Alumni Federation Board of Directors Meeting (NYU Club), 1983-02-01 (Box 265, Folder 5)
  - Statement on Draft Registration and Student Aid (NYU), 1983-02-02 (Box 265, Folder 6)
  - Luncheon to Introduce Alan Altschuler, Graduate School of Public Administration (NYU), 1983-02-03 (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Meeting, 1983-02-07 (Box 265, Folder 8)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1983-02-10 (Box 265, Folder 9)
  - Touche Ross Roundtable on the Management of Higher Education (Plaza Hotel, NY), 1983-02-14 (Box 265, Folder 10)
  - Executive Committee of the Faculty Council Meeting (NYU), 1983-02-15 (Box 265, Folder 11)
  - Talking Points Re: Claude Montana and Bergdorf Benefit for the Grey Art Gallery, 1983-02-15 (Box 265, Folder 12)
  - Press Conference on the Return of Men's Varsity Basketball at NYU, 1983-02-17 (Box 265, Folder 13)
  - Diane Belfer Luncheon (Palm Beach, FL), 1983-02-20 (Box 265, Folder 14)
  - Dinner Honoring Dean Stedman (NYU), 1983-02-04 (Box 265, Folder 15)
  - LBJ Symposium Commemorating FDR's 50th Anniversary (University of Texas), 1983-03-04 (Box 265, Folder 16)
  - Gallatin Vice-Chairmen and Dean's Breakfast (NYU), 1983-03-07 (Box 265, Folder 17)
  - Cunningham Dance Foundation Arts and Salute Dinner (Plaza Hotel, NY), 1983-03-07 (Box 265, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon Announcing New Development Campaign (NYU), 1983-03-08 (Box 265, Folder 19)
  - Remarks by Naomi Levine, John Brademas, George Heyman, and Laurence Tisch at Press Conference Announcing New Fundraising Campaign, 1983-03-08 (Box 266, Folder 1)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1983-03-10 (Box 265, Folder 2)
  - Introduction of Alexander Haig Public Policy Lecture (NYU), 1983-03-10 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Higher Education Conference (Washington, D.C.), 1983-03-11 (Box 266, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-03-14 (Box 266, Folder 5)
  - War, Peace, and the News Media Conference (NYU), 1983-03-18 (Box 266, Folder 6)
  - Conference of Graduate School of Business Administration Alumni (NYU), 1983-03-19 (Box 266, Folder 7)
  - Launch for Catalan Week at NYU, 1983-03-21 (Box 266, Folder 8)
  - Dedication of the Kaplan Cancer Center (NYU Medical Center), 1983-03-22 (Box 266, Folder 9)
  - Remarks Re: Fundraising, Inauguration of the Dental Center Ambassador Program, 1983-03-24 (Box 266, Folder 10)
  - Dinner for Alan Altshuler (NYU), 1983-03-24 (Box 266, Folder 11)
  - Colloquium on Catalonia in Modern Spain, 1983-03-24 (Box 266, Folder 12)
  - City Club of New York Luncheon, CUNY Graduate Center (New York, NY), 1983-03-25 (Box 266, Folder 13)
  - Archons of the Ecumenical Patriarchate Annual Banquet (Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NY), 1983-03-26 (Box 266, Folder 14)
  - Reception for Professor Gay Wilson Allen (NYU), 1983-04-04 (Box 266, Folder 15)
  - Joseph Lubin Memorial Service, 1983-04-07 (Box 266, Folder 16)
  - Rabbi Morris Lieberman Memorial Lecture, Baltimore Hebrew Congregation (Baltimore, MD), 1983-04-23 (Box 266, Folder 17)
  - Recording for the Blind Awards (Yale Club), 1983-04-27 (Box 266, Folder 18)
  - Giscard d'Estaing Lecture and Dinner (NYU), 1983-04-27 (Box 266, Folder 19)
  - Great Teacher Awards (NYU), 1983-04-28 (Box 266, Folder 20)
  - "Sailing Against the Wind," Boston University Conference on Arts and Education, 1983-04-29 (Box 267, Folder 1)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1983-05-05 (Box 267, Folder 2)
  - Testimony by James C. Finlay Before the Higher Education Commission (New York State Assembly), 1983-05-06 (Box 267, Folder 3)
  - "Public and Private Sectors," Graduate School of Public Administration Alumni Association (NYU), 1983-05-09 (Box 267, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-05-09 (Box 267, Folder 5)
  - Herbert H. Lehman Award Given to Martin Lipton, American Jewish Committee Dinner (New York, NY), 1983-05-10 (Box 267, Folder 6)
  - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies of New York (New York, NY), 1983-05-10 (Box 267, Folder 7)
  - "Engaging a Whole World: The Humanities in the 1980s," The President's Forum at Claremont University (Claremont, CA), 1983-05-13 (Box 267, Folder 8)
  - Claremont Graduate School Commencement Address (Claremont, CA), 1983-05-14 (Box 267, Folder 9)
  - Dinner Honoring Dean Daniel Griffiths (NYU Club), 1983-05-20 (Box 267, Folder 10)
  - SUNY Albany Commencement Address (Albany, NY), 1983-05-22 (Box 267, Folder 11)
  - Dedication of the Third Floor (Bobst Library), 1983-05-23 (Box 267, Folder 12)
  - Annual Alumni Dinner (NYU Club), 1983-05-24 (Box 267, Folder 13)
  - Subcommittee on Labor, Health and Human Services, U.S. House of Representatives (Washington, D.C.), 1983-05-24 (Box 267, Folder 14)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-05-31 (Box 267, Folder 15)
  - Pre-Commencement Dinner for the Board of Trustees (NYU), 1983-06-02 (Box 267, Folder 16)
  - School of Medicine Commencement (NYU), 1983-06-02 (Box 267, Folder 17)
  - NYU All-University Commencement, 1983-06-03 (Box 267, Folder 18)
  - University of Massachusetts Lowell Commencement Address (Lowell, MA), 1983-06-04 (Box 267, Folder 19)
  - Eastern Regional Conference of National State Budget Officers (Albany, NY), 1983-06-07 (Box 267, Folder 20)
  - Introductory Remarks for Claiborne Pell, American Council on the Arts Board Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1983-06-09 (Box 267, Folder 21)
  - Meeting of the Congressional Intern Program (Washington, D.C.), 1983-06-09 (Box 267, Folder 22)
  - Shady Side Academy Commencement Address (Pittsburgh, PA), 1983-06-10 (Box 267, Folder 23)
  - Dinner Honoring Reverend Boardman W. Kathan (NYU), 1983-06-14 (Box 268, Folder 1)
  - Life Gallatin Reception (NYU), 1983-06-14 (Box 268, Folder 2)
  - Induction Dinner of Dental School's Omega Chapter of Omicron Kappa Upsilon (New York, NY), 1983-06-15 (Box 268, Folder 3)
  - Introduction to Duel for the Dunes, by Norma Schaeffer and Kay Franklin, 1983-06-23 (Box 268, Folder 4)
  - Fifth National Conference on Communications Technology in Education and Training, 1983-06-27 (Box 268, Folder 5)
  - Birkbeck College, University of London (London, England), 1983-06-30 (Box 268, Folder 6)
  - Foreword to Lifelong Learning Leaders Retreat Report, 1983-07-01 (Box 268, Folder 7)
  - Chapter on International Education in U.S., 1983-07-07 (Box 268, Folder 8)
  - Talking Points for Graduate Education Hearing, National Commission on Student Financial Assistance, 1983-07-07 (Box 268, Folder 9)
  - French-American Foundation Dinner (New York, NY), 1983-07-18 (Box 268, Folder 10)
  - NYU-High School for the Humanities Project Press Conference and Reception (NYU), 1983-07-25 (Box 268, Folder 11)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures Annual Meeting (San Antonio, TX), 1983-08-09 (Box 268, Folder 12)
  - New York Times Article Draft, 1983-08-12 (Box 268, Folder 13)
  - Design Magazine Article, 1983-08-15 (Box 268, Folder 14)
  - Written Piece for Cooper-Hewitt Museum Publication, 1983-09-01 (Box 268, Folder 15)
  - Speech Re: the Kennedy Assassination, 1983-09-02 (Box 268, Folder 16)
  - Student Convocation (NYU), 1983-09-12 (Box 268, Folder 17)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-09-14 (Box 268, Folder 18)
  - BobCat Press Conference, 1983-09-15 (Box 268, Folder 19)
  - Montclair State College 75th Anniversary (Montclair, NJ), 1983-09-20 (Box 268, Folder 20)
  - Inaugural Symposium of the Indiana University Instititute for Advanced Study (Bloomington, IN), 1983-09-26 (Box 268, Folder 21)
  - All-University Graduate Student Reception (NYU), 1983-09-28 (Box 268, Folder 22)
  - Stephen Chan House Press Conference (Institute of Fine Art), 1983-09-29 (Box 268, Folder 23)
  - Stephen Chan House Dedication Ceremonies (Institute of Fine Art), 1983-09-30 (Box 268, Folder 24)
  - The Cosmetic, Toiletry and Fragrance Association Luncheon (Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NY), 1983-09-30 (Box 268, Folder 25)
  - 35th Annual Conference of Association of Graduate Schools (College Park, MD), 1983-10-03 (Box 268, Folder 26)
  - Gallatin Associates Dinner, 1983-10-06 (Box 268, Folder 27)
  - 2nd Annual Faculty Convocation (NYU), 1983-10-11 (Box 268, Folder 28)
  - Penthouse Dinner for Father Theodore M. Hesburgh (NYU), 1983-10-17 (Box 268, Folder 29)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1983-10-17 (Box 268, Folder 30)
  - Accountants Club of America Luncheon (Harvard Club, NY), 1983-10-27 (Box 268, Folder 31)
  - International Relations Study Center at NYU, 1983-10-27 (Box 269, Folder 1)
  - Modern Greek Association Symposium (NYU), 1983-10-27 (Box 269, Folder 2)
  - Association of Independent Colleges and Universities of New Jersey (Monmouth College, West Long Branch, NJ), 1983-10-28 (Box 269, Folder 3)
  - Parents' Day Receptions (NYU), 1983-11-06 (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Trustees Scholars Dinner (NYU), 1983-11-09 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture Dinner (NYU), 1983-11-10 (Box 269, Folder 6)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Ceremony (NYU), 1983-11-17 (Box 269, Folder 7)
  - Atlantic Institute for International Affairs (Washington, D.C.), 1983-11-18 (Box 269, Folder 8)
  - Cyprus Children's Fund Dinner (New York, NY), 1983-11-18 (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - Remarks Re: High Schools and Universities (Washington, D.C.), 1983-11-22 (Box 269, Folder 10)
  - Dean's Day at the School of Business and Public Administration (NYU), 1983-12-03 (Box 269, Folder 11)
  - Welcome Remarks by Brademas and Laurence Tisch, Dinner Honoring King Juan Carlos I of Spain (NYU), 1983-10-06 (Box 269, Folder 12)
  - Convocation Honoring King Juan Carlos I of Spain (NYU), 1983-12-07 (Box 269, Folder 13)
  - "The Road After 1984: High Technology and Human Freedom," Smithsonian Institution (Washington, D.C.), 1983-12-08 (Box 269, Folder 14)
  - Smithsonian Symposium, National Museum of American History (Washington, D.C.), 1983-12-08 (Box 269, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Network Press Conference and Board Meeting (NYU), 1983-12-13 (Box 269, Folder 16)
  - Article for Change Magazine, 1984-01-13 (Box 269, Folder 17)
  - Upward Bound Press Conference (NYU), 1984-01-24 (Box 269, Folder 18)
  - Little Forum's Annual Dinner (Bronxville, NY), 1984-01-26 (Box 269, Folder 19)
  - Annual Midwinter Conference of the New York State Council of School Superintendents (Albany, NY), 1984-01-29 (Box 269, Folder 20)
  - Talking Points for Brooklyn Bridge Centennial Videotape (New York, NY), 1984-02-06 (Box 269, Folder 21)
  - Graduate and Professional Financial Aid Council (Arlington, VA), 1984-02-14 (Box 269, Folder 22)
  - Japanese Chamber of Commerce of New York Lunch (New York, NY), 1984-02-23 (Box 269, Folder 23)
  - Dinner Honoring Dr. Robert M. Warner (NYU), 1984-02-23 (Box 269, Folder 24)
  - Dinner Honoring New Trustees (NYU), 1984-02-28 (Box 269, Folder 25)
  - Dinner for Opening of Picasso Exhibition, Guggenheim Museum (New York, NY), 1984-02-29 (Box 269, Folder 26)
  - "Afternoon at Washington Square" Event, 1984-03-04 (Box 269, Folder 27)
  - Society of Foreign Consuls (New York, NY), 1984-03-04 (Box 269, Folder 28)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1984-03-08 (Box 269, Folder 29)
  - Trustees-Faculty Council Reception (NYU), 1984-03-12 (Box 269, Folder 30)
  - Presidents, Vice Presidents, and Deans of Education from Public and Independent Universities in New York, 1984-03-13 (Box 269, Folder 31)
  - Don Fuqua and Jim Wright Lunch (Washington, D.C.), 1984-03-14 (Box 269, Folder 32)
  - Real Estate Institute Annual Urban Leadership Award Dinner (NYU), 1984-03-14 (Box 269, Folder 33)
  - Conference on Education: Action for Interaction (Stamford, CT), 1984-03-15 (Box 269, Folder 34)
  - Public Affairs Forum Penthouse Dinner (NYU), 1984-03-15 (Box 269, Folder 35)
  - Middle States Evaluation Dinner (NYU), 1984-03-18 (Box 270, Folder 1)
  - Dean Joseph H. Taggart Memorial Service (NYU), 1984-03-21 (Box 270, Folder 2)
  - NYU Institute of Environmental Medicine (Sterling Forest, NY), 1984-03-23 (Box 270, Folder 3)
  - J. Edward Farnum Public Lecture at the Woodrow Wilson School of Public and International Affairs (Princeton University, Princeton, NJ), 1984-03-26 (Box 270, Folder 4)
  - Lunch Honoring Caroline and Joseph S. Gruss Visiting Professorship in Talmudic Law (NYU), 1984-03-28 (Box 270, Folder 5)
  - Harold Weill Medal Presentation Dinner, School of Law (NYU), 1984-03-28 (Box 270, Folder 6)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education, Committee on Education and Labor (Washington, D.C.), 1984-03-29 (Box 270, Folder 7)
  - Message for Interview with Zubin Mehta, Gallatin Division Great Artist Series (NYU), 1984-04-04 (Box 270, Folder 8)
  - Dedication and Dinner for Ruth and George Farkas Auditorium of Alumni Hall (NYU), 1984-04-10 (Box 270, Folder 9)
  - Dinner Honoring Frances Todman (NYU), 1984-04-11 (Box 270, Folder 10)
  - Lunch Honoring Michael Brock, Warden of Nuffield College (NYU), 1984-04-12 (Box 270, Folder 11)
  - Dinner Honoring Maestro Andrés Segovia, 1984-04-14 (Box 270, Folder 12)
  - National University Continuing Education Association Annual Conference (Atlanta, GA), 1984-04-17 (Box 270, Folder 13)
  - Presentation of "Award of Honor" Medals from Fine Arts Federation of New York to NYU, 1984-04-18 (Box 270, Folder 14)
  - Dinner Honoring Nicholas Wahl (NYU), 1984-04-18 (Box 270, Folder 15)
  - Reception for Alumni of the University Heights Campus (NYU), 1984-04-19 (Box 270, Folder 16)
  - Executive Briefing on the Ada Computer Language and Compiler (Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences, NYU), 1984-04-23 (Box 270, Folder 17)
  - Seminar and Dinner Honoring Raymond Carr (NYU), 1984-04-23-1984-04-25 (Box 270, Folder 18)
  - New York State Regional Economists Society (New York, NY), 1984-04-24 (Box 270, Folder 19)
  - Founders Day (NYU), 1984-04-26 (Box 270, Folder 20)
  - Sermon, Holocaust Remembrance Service (NYU), 1984-04-26 (Box 270, Folder 21)
  - Mayors Forum on Urban Policy (NYU), 1984-04-27 (Box 270, Folder 22)
  - Phi Kappa Phi Induction Ceremony (Penascola, FL), 1984-04-27 (Box 270, Folder 23)
  - University of West Florida Commencement Address (Penascola, FL), 1984-04-28 (Box 270, Folder 24)
  - Westside Community Conference, Columbia University (New York, NY), 1984-04-29 (Box 270, Folder 25)
  - Faculty of the School of Medicine (NYU), 1984-04-30 (Box 270, Folder 26)
  - Grants Magazine Article, 1984-04-30 (Box 270, Folder 27)
  - Seminar on "Ideology/Politics," Jornadas Catalanas Conference (Spanish Institute, NY), 1984-05-02 (Box 270, Folder 28)
  - New York State Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development Meeting (Kiamesha Lake, NY), 1984-05-06 (Box 270, Folder 29)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU), 1984-05-07 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Annual Alumni Dinner (NYU Club), 1984-05-15 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Reception for Israeli Poet Yehuda Amichai (NYU), 1984-05-16 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - 25-Year Service Awards (NYU), 1984-05-16 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - Lecture by and Dinner Honoring Sidney Hook (NYU), 1984-05-17 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Global Crossroads Panel (Washington, D.C.), 1984-05-18 (Box 271, Folder 6)
  - Drew University Commencement Address (Madison, NJ), 1984-05-19 (Box 271, Folder 7)
  - Cocktail Reception Honoring New Life Members of the Albert Gallatin Associates (NYU), 1984-05-21 (Box 271, Folder 8)
  - Presentation of Citations to Honorary Degree Recipients, Board of Trustees Dinner (NYU), 1984-05-23 (Box 271, Folder 9)
  - NYU All-University Commencement, 1984-05-24 (Box 271, Folder 10)
  - Cocktail Reception Honoring Dean William F. May, Graduate School of Business Administration (NYU), 1984-06-07 (Box 271, Folder 11)
  - Albert Gallatin Fellows Dinner (NYU), 1984-06-07 (Box 271, Folder 12)
  - Luncheon of the Propeller Club of the United States (Athens, Greece), 1984-06-12 (Box 271, Folder 13)
  - "Current Trends in American Education: A Panoramic View," Annual Alumni Day of Athens College (Athens, Greece), 1984-06-12 (Box 271, Folder 14)
  - American Community Schools of Athens Commencement Address (Athens, Greece), 1984-06-12 (Box 271, Folder 15)
  - Ecumenical Doxology Celebration of Independence Day (New York, NY), 1984-07-04 (Box 271, Folder 16)
  - Local 23-25, ILGWU College Textbook Scholarship Awards Ceremony (New York, NY), 1984-08-16 (Box 271, Folder 17)
  - Accepting the American Political Science Association's Hubert H. Humphrey Award (Washington, D.C.), 1984-08-30 (Box 271, Folder 18)
  - "The Research University, Graduate Education and Public Policy", Indiana University, 1984-09 (Box 271, Folder 19)
  - NYU-Scholastic Institute Press Conference, 1984-09-10 (Box 271, Folder 20)
  - "Brown Plus Thirty" Banquet (NYU), 1984-09-12 (Box 271, Folder 21)
  - NYU Student Convocation, 1984-09-13 (Box 271, Folder 22)
  - Planned Giving Seminar (NYU), 1984-09-13 (Box 271, Folder 23)
  - Washington Square Park Crafts and Antiques Fair (New York, NY), 1984-09-22 (Box 271, Folder 24)
  - Urban Research Center Luncheon (NYU), 1984-09-24 (Box 271, Folder 25)
  - Welcome Remarks, Symposium Honoring Father J. Bryan Hehir (NYU), 1984-09-24 (Box 271, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Student Orientation (NYU), 1984-09-25 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Presentation of Eduardo Garrigues, Author of The Grass Rain, (The Spanish Institute, NY), 1984-09-25 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Holy Trinity Cathedral Lecture (New York, NY), 1984-09-26 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Visit of Central American University Rectors (NYU), 1984-09-26 (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Accent Magazine Article, 1984-10-01 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - Daedalus Interview, 1984-10-01 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Reception Honoring Dean Richard West, Graduate School of Business Administration (New York, NY), 1984-10-03 (Box 272, Folder 7)
  - National Council for Children and Television Luncheon (New York, NY), 1984-10-05 (Box 272, Folder 8)
  - Spain Talking Points (Spain), 1984-10-06 (Box 272, Folder 9)
  - Italy Talking Points, 1984-10-06 (Box 272, Folder 10)
  - Convocation Honoring Sir Steven Runciman (NYU), 1984-10-18 (Box 272, Folder 11)
  - Dinner Honoring Sir Steven Runciman (NYU), 1984-10-18 (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - Inauguration of President Jerry Lee, Gallaudet College (Washington, D.C.), 1984-10-19 (Box 272, Folder 13)
  - Dinner for Robert K. Massie, 1984-10-19 (Box 272, Folder 14)
  - Presentation of Nathan S. Kline Medal of Merit to Rosalynn Carter (Orangeburg, NY), 1984-10-22 (Box 272, Folder 15)
  - Introduction of Charles Bowsher Lecture (NYU), 1984-10-22 (Box 272, Folder 16)
  - Press Conference for the School of Continuing Education (NYU), 1984-10-23 (Box 272, Folder 17)
  - Opening of the 26th Street Dormitory (NYU), 1984-10-24 (Box 272, Folder 18)
  - Remarks by Laurence Tisch, Opening of the 26th Street Dormitory (NYU), 1984-10-24 (Box 272, Folder 19)
  - "Election '84: Implications for Education," Wright State University (Dayton, OH), 1984-10-25 (Box 272, Folder 20)
  - Dinner Honoring Marie Schwartz, NYU College of Dentistry (New York, NY), 1984-10-29 (Box 272, Folder 21)
  - "Resolved that Education is a Federal Concern: A Congressman's View," Gannon Seminar, Fordham University (New York, NY), 1984-10-30 (Box 272, Folder 22)
  - "Education on the National Agenda: Perspectives and Prospects," Gannon Lecture, Fordham University (New York, NY), 1984-10-31 (Box 272, Folder 23)
  - Japan Center Conference Lunch (New York, NY), 1984-11-02 (Box 272, Folder 24)
  - Campaign Gala (NYU), 1984-11-03 (Box 272, Folder 25)
  - Parents' Day (NYU), 1984-11-04 (Box 272, Folder 26)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting (NYU), 1984-11-07 (Box 272, Folder 27)
  - "Engaging a Whole World: The Humanities in the 1980s," Convocation at Fairfield University (Fairfield, CT), 1984-11-08 (Box 272, Folder 28)
  - Dedication of the Rusk Institute (NYU), 1984-11-09 (Box 272, Folder 29)
  - Dinner Honoring Eppie Lederer (NY), 1984-11-10 (Box 272, Folder 30)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Dinner, College of Business and Public Administration (New York, NY), 1984-11-12 (Box 272, Folder 31)
  - Reception in Rubin Dining Hall (NYU), 1984-11-12 (Box 272, Folder 32)
  - Dinner Honoring Sir Ronald Syme (NYU), 1984-11-14 (Box 272, Folder 33)
  - Faculty Convocation (NYU), 1984-11-14 (Box 272, Folder 34)
  - American Council of Life Insurance (Boston, MA), 1984-11-14 (Box 273, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1984-11-15 (Box 273, Folder 2)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture (NYU), 1984-11-15 (Box 273, Folder 3)
  - "The Elections are Over: What Next," Lecture, School of Law Alumni Day (NYU), 1984-11-17 (Box 273, Folder 4)
  - Cocktail Reception for the Spanish Institute in Honor of Don Juan de Borbón (NYU), 1984-11-17 (Box 273, Folder 5)
  - School of Continuing Education 50th Anniversary Celebration, Presentation of Award to Ed Koch (Gracie Mansion, NY), 1984-11-19 (Box 273, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Resources Network Luncheon (NYU), 1984-11-20 (Box 273, Folder 7)
  - Remarks Preceding Lecture by Angelos Angelopoulos (NYU), 1984-11-20 (Box 273, Folder 8)
  - Presentation of a Doctorate of Humane Letters to Archbishop Iakovos (NYU), 1984-11-25 (Box 273, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Institute for International Affairs (NYU), 1984-11-29 (Box 273, Folder 10)
  - Banco de la Provincia de Buenos Aires Seminar (New York, NY), 1984-12-03 (Box 273, Folder 11)